<resources>
    <string name="app_name">BongoBuild</string>
    <string name="app_name_description_splash">Buy To Make Things Best</string>
    <string name="title_home">Home</string>
    <string name="title_dashboard">View Products</string>
    <string name="title_notifications">Notifications</string>
    <string name="title_account">Account</string>
    <string name="title_any_ques">Query</string>
    <string name="drawerOpen">Drawer Open</string>
    <string name="drawerClose">Drawer Close</string>
    <string name="plumbing">Choose your Product Type</string>
    <string name="product_description_hint">Product Variations</string>
    <string name="product_description_hint1">Bricks Type</string>
    <string name="product_description_hint3">Plumbing Materials</string>
    <string name="product_description_hint2">Construction Chemicals</string>
    <string name="product_description_hint4">MM and SS Materials</string>
    <string name="product_description_hint5">Electrical Products</string>
    <string name="product_description_hint6">Lighting Gallery</string>
    <string name="product_description_hint7">Tiles Gallery</string>
    <string name="product_description_hint8">Thi Aluminium</string>
    <string name="product_description_hint9">Interior Materials</string>
    <string name="product_description_hint10">Hardware and Tools</string>
    <string name="product_description_hint11">Paint Gallery</string>
    <string name="rod_products_heading"> BSRM Rod</string>
    <string name="core_product_text_description">Meghna Cement Mills Ltd is the first manufacturing unit of Bashundhara Group
        and it is one of the largest cement industries in the country producing nearly 1 million metric tons a year.
        The Meghna Cement Mills Ltd is an International Standard Organization (ISO 9001: 2008) certified company having
        accreditation of manufacturing products for both domestic and international markets. The company is listed with both
        Dhaka and Chittagong Stock Exchanges,
        the two bourses of the country since 1995 and 1996 respectively.
        The company markets its product under the registered trade mark "King Brand Cement".</string>
    <string name="core_product_heading">Meghna Cement</string>

    <string name="core_product_description_rod"> A Leading Steel Manufacturer

    BSRM is the leading steel manufacturing
        company and one of the prominent corporate houses
        in Bangladesh. Over the years, BSRM steel products have been chosen solely for building major National landmarks and infrastructures. To name a few, the Padma Bridge, Rooppur Neuclear Power Plant, Hatirjheel Project, Zillur Rahman Flyover, Mayor Hanif Flyover and Shah Amanat Bridge were built with BSRM.
</string>

    A Leading Steel Manufacturer

    BSRM is the leading steel manufacturing company and one of the prominent corporate houses in
    Bangladesh. Over the years, BSRM steel products have been chosen solely for building major
    National landmarks and infrastructures. To name a few, the Padma Bridge, Rooppur Neuclear Power
    Plant, Hatirjheel Project, Zillur Rahman Flyover, Mayor Hanif Flyover and Shah Amanat Bridge
    were built with BSRM.

</resources>
